One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Sandy Island (The Kingdom of Alabasta)
Sandy Adası (Alabasta Krallığı)
Sir Crocodile, the Pirate
Korsan Sör Crocodile
The Port Town of Nanohana
Liman Şehri, Nanohana
Sir Crocodile...
Crocodile-sama...
Crocodile!
Crocodile!
Huh?
Ha?
Ahh... Sir Crocodile!
Ahh... Crocodile-sama!
I knew he'd come!
Geleceğinizi biliyordum!
Crocodile?!
Crocodile mı?!
From the Seven Warlords...?
Shichibukai olan mı?
Silence, you fools!
Sessiz olun, aptallar!
I've only come for that pirate's head!
Sadece korsanların başı için geldim!
He's amazing...
Harika birisi...
He always says that but saves us anyway!
Hep bunu söylüyor ama yine de imdadımıza yetişiyor!
Hurray for Crocodile!
Çok yaşa, Crocodile!
Alabasta's guardian deity!
Alabasta'nın koruyucu meleği!
Crocodile!
Crocodile!
King of the desert! Crocodile!
Çöl kralı! Crocodile!
Sir Crocodile One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea Former Bounty: 81 Million Belly
Sör Crocodile Shichibukai Eski Kelle Ödülü: 81 Milyon Beli
Well, call me what you will.
Bana istediğinizi diyebilirsiniz.
Don't just think you can waltz in and plunder this country, pirates.
Bu ülkeye öyle rahatça girip talan edebileceğinizi düşünmeyin, korsanlar.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Aren't you underestimating us?
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Bizi küçümsemiyor musun?
You thinking of taking us all on by yourself?!
Hepimizi tek başına mı yeneceksin?!
You sold out to the authorities, you government dog!
Otoriteye sattın kendini, seni hükûmet iti!
You think you're some kinda hero?!
Kendini kahraman falan mı sanıyorsun?!
Those who wish to live, lay on the ground.
Yaşamak isteyenler, yere yatsın.
Is he stupid?! He's wide open!
Aptal mı bu? Etrafını sardık!
Get him! He won't keep us from this town's money and valuables!
Haklayın şunu! Bu şehrin ganimetlerinden alıkoyamaz bizi!
– Yeah!
– Aynen!
Is this really a famous Warlord?!
Bu muymuş Shichibukai?!
I'm a whole different caliber of pirate, swine.
Korsanlardan farklı bir seviyedeyim, seni domuz.
Crocodile!
Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile again...
Yine Crocodile...
Alubarna Palace Kingdom of Alabasta
Alubarna Sarayı Alabasta Krallığı
He was one step ahead again?
Yine mi bir adım öndeydi?
By the time we got to Nanohana, it was all over.
Nanohana'ya vardığımızda her şey çoktan hallolmuştu.
I see.
Anlıyorum.
Either way, it's fine as long as the citizens are safe.
Önemli olan, halkın güvende olması.
Nefertari Cobra King of Alabasta
Nefertari Cobra Alabasta Kralı
We are indebted to him.
Ona borçlandık.
There's no mistake.
Hata yok.
Our ship is heading to Alabasta.
Gemi, Alabasta'ya gidiyor.
Luffy! Don't lie!
Luffy! Yalan söyleme!
Tell me what you know.
Bildiklerini anlat.
Hey, why are you looking away? Look me in the eyes!
Hey, nereye bakıyorsun? Gözlerimin içine bak!
Well... um, really... I don't know anything.
Yani... şey, hiçbir şey bilmiyorum.
Then answer me this.
O zaman söyle.
For this trip to Alabasta, I carefully procured and divided enough food for eight people,
Bu Alabasta seyahati için sekiz kişilik yiyeceği dikkatle ayarlayıp pay ettim,
so how did it disappear during the night?
peki gece vakti nasıl oldu da yok oldu?
It's pointless to try and fool me! You've got the worst poker face.
Beni kandıramazsın! Yüzünden her şey okunuyor.
Hey, you have something around your mouth.
Hey, ağzının kenarında bir şey var.
Ah! Shoot! Crumbs?!
Ah! Eyvah! Yemek mi?!
It was you!
Sendin!
C'mon...
Hay...
Ah, Nami... You saw, right?
Ah, Nami-san, gördünüz değil mi?
The large rat trap just won't do anymore.
O büyük fare kapanı da yetmiyor artık.
Please buy a fridge with a lock.
Lütfen kilidi olan bir buzdolabı alalım.
Well...
Peki...
I'll think about it...
Düşüneceğim...
since our lives may depend on it.
Hayatlarımız buna bağlı.
Hm?
Ha?
Well then! We'd better catch something for Sanji.
Pekâlâ! Sanji-kun için bir şeyler yakalasak iyi olur.
Hey, any luck fishing?
Hey, var mı bir şeyler?
W-Well...
Ş-Şey...
I feel lucky...
Harika hissettiriyor...
I seriously can't turn my back for a second!
Bir saniye arkamı dönemiyorum!
Ahh... I'm starving.
Öf... Öleceğim açlıktan.
The fish aren't biting at all.
Balık da yok ortalıkta.
Luffy! It's your fault! I mean, you even ate the bait!
Luffy! Senin suçun! Yemleri bile yedin!
If we don't have bait, the fish won't bite!
Yemimiz yoksa, balık tabii gelmez!
You ate some too!
Sen de yedin biraz.
That's... I only ate what was stuck to the lid of the bait box.
Yani... kapağına sıkışmıştı, onu yedim.
Luffy. Usopp. Have you caught anything?
Luffy-san. Usopp-san. Bir şeyler yakalayabildiniz mi?
Karoo! Oh, no!
Karoo! Olamaz!
He might catch us a shark.
Belki köpek balığı yakalayabilir.
I wanna catch a sea king.
Deniz kralı istiyorum ben.
Just what do you two think you're doing to Karoo?!
Siz ikiniz Karoo'ya ne yaptığınızı sanıyorsunuz?
What's that?
O da ne?
What the heck is that?
O ne be?
Maybe it's cotton candy.
Galiba pamuk şeker.
I'll go get Nami!
Nami-san'ı çağıracağım!
Hmm?
Hmm?
Nami, it's urgent! Come see!
Nami-san, çok acil! Gel!
Ahh... don't worry. It's nothing. It's just steam.
Ahh... endişelenmeyin. Bir şey yok. Buhar sadece.
Steam is coming up from the sea?
Denizden buhar mı çıkıyor?
Yeah. It's a hot spot.
Evet. Sıcak bölgedeyiz.
What the heck is that?
O da ne öyle?
It's an area where magma spews.
Orası magmanın aktığı bir bölge.
There's an undersea volcano below that area.
O bölgenin altında bir deniz altı yanardağı var.
Oh?
Ha?
A volcano even though it's undersea?
Su altında bir yanardağ mı?
That's right. There are more volcanoes under the water than above it.
Aynen öyle. Suda, karadakinden fazla yanardağ bulunuyor.
Whoa...
Ohaaa...
Who cares? We can't eat it.
Bize ne? Yenmiyor sonuçta.
With an active volcano here, a new island will be born
Burada aktif bir yanardağ olduğu için, binlerce hatta on binlerce...
over thousands— or tens of thousands—of years.
yıl içinde yeni bir ada oluşacak.
You're so cool, Nami!
Harikasın, Nami-san!
Tens of thousands of years... I wonder if I can live that long.
On binlerce yıl... Acaba o kadar yaşar mıyım?
Nah, humans don't live that long.
Yok be, insan ömrü o kadar uzun değil.
Caught anything yet?
Nasıl gidiyor?
Oh, Sanji. I'm hungry. Cook something.
Aa, Sanji. Acıktım. Yapsana bir şeyler.
You guys are hopeless.
Sizden adam olmaz.
I'll go upturn the storage to see if anything's left.
Deponun altını üstüne getireceğim, bir şey kalmıştır belki.
Gah! It reeks of sulfur!
İyy! Sülfür kokuyor!
We can't see a thing with steam everywhere!
Buhardan hiçbir şey göremiyoruz!
Bear with it. We should be through it soon.
Dayanın. Birazdan geçecek.
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Bay 2, Bon Clay-sama!
What is it?!
Ne var?!
There's smoke at twelve o'clock!
Saat 12 yönünde duman var!
So what?! Sail right through it!
Ne olmuş?! İçinden geçin!
Just so we're clear, if we don't take out Mr. 3, I'm toast!
Şunu netleştirelim, Bay 3'ten kurtulamazsak işim biter!
Yes, sir! Going in!
Başüstüne! Giriyoruz!
What's with the fog?
Bu sis ne ya?
We can't see far!
Önümüzü göremiyoruz!
We got through!
Atlattık!
Ahh! Mr. 2 Bon Kurei is gone!
Ahh! Bay 2, Bon Clay-sama yok!
Check inside!
Her yere bakın!
We can't find him!
Bulamıyoruz!
Can't be!
Olamaz!
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Bay 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Whoa...!
Oha...!
Aw, poop!
Tanrım!
This duck came from out of nowhere, and I jumped to it?!
Neden aniden karşıma çıkan ördeğin üstüne atladım ki?!
– Is he a human? – Dunno...
– İnsan mı? – Bilmiyorum...
Oh?! Wahhh!
Ne?! Vahhh!
Help me! Please!
Yardım edin! Lütfen!
I can't swim! I can't swi–
Yüzemiyorum! Yüzemi–
I thought I'd die...
Öleceğimi sandım…
Well... I'm very swan-swan.
Ama şimdi, tam anlamıyla kuğu gibiyim.
"Bon Kurei"
"Bon Clay"
To think that I was saved by pirates who are total strangers...
Hiç tanımadığım korsanlar tarafından kurtarılmak…
I will never forget your kindness!
Bu iyiliğinizi daima hatırlayacağım!
Also, may I have a cup of warm soup?
Bir de, sıcak çorba alabilir miyim?
– Like we have it!
-Yok ki!
We're the ones who are hungry!
Aç olan biziz!
Oh! Hey there, you!
Aha!
Aren't you just the cutest?!
Ne kadar tatlısın öyle!
Totally my type! I could just eat you up!
Tam benliksin! Yerim seni!
What a weirdo...
Rahatsız...
So you can't swim, huh?
Demek yüzemiyorsun, ha?
That's right. I ate a devil fruit.
Evet. Şeytan meyvesi yedim de.
Really? What kind of fruit?
Cidden mi? Ne tür bir meyve?
Well, well... All we can do now is wait for my ship to come pick me up.
Yani, şimdi gemimin gelmesini beklemekten başka çarem yok.
So perhaps I'll put on a little show.
Ufak bir gösteri fena olmaz gibi.
Behold my power!
Gücüme iyi bakın!
What are you...?!
Ne yapıyor...?!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Bekle! Bekle! Bekle!
Didn't I say this would be a "show"?
Gösteri yapacağımı söylemedim mi?
What?!
Ne?!
Nobody's clowning here!
Bunun şakası yok.
He's me!
Aha ben!
Surprised?! Surprised?! Surprised?!
Şaşırdınız mı?! Şaşırdınız mı?!
If I touch my face with my left hand...
Sol elimle yüzüme dokunursam...
See?! Back to normal!
Gördünüz mü?! Normale döndüm!
This is the power of the Clone-Clone Fruit!
Klon-Klon Meyvesi'nin gücü bu!
Even his voice...
Sesi bile değişiyor...
His body was also the same!
Fiziği de aynıydı!
A-Amazing!
H-Harika!
There!
İşte!
Ah! Come to think of it, I didn't have to knock you down.
Ah! Şimdi düşününce, seni yere sermeme gerek yoktu.
Because look...!
Çünkü bakın...!
All that's needed is
Tek gereken,
to touch your faces with my right hand.
sağ elimle yüzünüze dokunmam.
As you can see, I can
Ve gördüğünüz gibi, ben...
mimic anyone!
herkese dönüşebilirim!
Bodies too!
Beden de dahil.
Ouch!
Ah!
Stop that!
Kes şunu!
Hey, are you all right?
Hey, iyi misin?
Ow, ow, ow...
Ah, ah, ah...
Oh, my... Unfortunately, that's all I'm willing to show of my power.
Ah... Üzgünüm ama daha fazla gücümü gösteremem.
You're the best! Show some more!
Harikasın! Biraz daha göster!
Ahh... Well... if you insist... I guess I'll show more!
Ahh... Şey... Madem ısrarcısınız... Daha fazlasını gösterebilirim!
Yeah! Show it! Show it!
Evet! Göster! Göster!
It's not that exciting.
Çok da etkileyici değil.
Well then, I guess I'll show... We wanna see! We wanna see!
Göstereceğim galiba... Göster bize!
Furthermore, I'm equipped with a memory feature!
Üstelik, bir hafıza yeteneğim de mevcut!
Here we go!
Başlıyoruz!
Whoa!
Vay!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
Dön! Dön! Dön!
Ridiculous!
Aptallık!
Spin! Spin!
Dön! Dön!
So, did you like my special talent?
Özel yeteneğimi beğendiniz mi?
It's rare for me to show it off.
Herkese göstermem.
Cool!
Çok iyi!
Nobody's clowning here!
Bunun şakası yok! Bunun şakası yok!
Oh, whatever!
Öf, neyse!
That's my ship!
İşte benim gemim!
Amazing! Amazing! He's...
Harika! Harika! O...
Ciao!
Görüşürüz!
"Bon Kurei"
"Bon Clay"
It's already time to say goodbye? What a shame.
Şimdiden ayrılık vakti geldi mi? Kader utansın.
– What?!
– Ne?!
Please don't go!
Lütfen gitme!
Chin up, and don't be sad!
Metin olun ve üzülmeyin!
Every voyage contains some farewells.
Her yolculuğun içinde vedalar vardır.
But... never forget this:
Ama siz... bunu asla unutmayın:
Friendship...
Arkadaşlık,
has nothing to do with how long we've known each other.
ne kadar zamandır tanıştığımızla alakalı değildir.
Don't cry!
Ağlamayın!
Let's meet again!
Tekrar görüşelim!
Now, let's go, boys!
Şimdi, gidelim, çocuklar!
Yes, sir! Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Başüstüne! Bay 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Mr. 2?!
Bay 2 mi?!
So then he's... Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Öyleyse o... Bay 2, Bon Clay'di!
Vivi! You've never seen him?!
Vivi! Daha önce onu görmedin mi?!
No... I've never met Mr. 2 or the Mr. 1 duo.
Hayır… Bay 2 ve Bay 1 çiftlerini hiç görmedim.
I don't know their powers, either.
Güçlerini de bilmiyorum.
Though I've heard rumors...
Bir iki şey duydum ama.
Supposedly, Mr. 2 is...
Söylentilere göre, Bay 2...
a lanky ballerina who talks with an effeminate voice.
Kadın gibi konuşan kaba vücutlu bir balerinmiş.
He always wears a swan coat that displays "Bon Kurei" on its back.
Her zaman arkasında ''Bon Clay" yazan kuğu paltosu giyiyormuş.
– You should've noticed!
– Fark etmeliydin!
What's the matter, Vivi?
Sorun ne, Vivi?
Among the faces that he pulled from his past memories...
Hafıza yeteneğiyle gösterdiği...
from his memory feature...
yüzler arasında...
I saw my father's face...
babamın yüzünü gördüm.
the face of Alabasta's king, Nefertari Cobra!
Alabasta'nın kralı, Nefertari Cobra'nın yüzü!
If, for example, you could mimic a king,
Eğer kralın kılığına girebilseydin,
you could get away with just about anything.
istediğin her şeyi yapabilirdin.
We let a troublesome guy slip away, huh?
Baş belası birini elimizden kaçırdık, ha?
So he was our enemy?
Düşmanımız mıydı yani?
He's one hell of a problem if he's on the opposing side.
Eğer karşı taraftaysa ciddi bir sorun olur.
If he realizes that we're his enemies...
Düşman olduğumuzu fark ederse...
If he transforms into one of us using his memory feature,
hafıza yeteneğiyle, birimizin kılığına girebilir.
we won't be able to trust our own friends.
Arkadaşlarımıza bile güvenemeyiz.
You sure?
Öyle mi?
Listen, Luffy–
Dinle, Luffy–
Wait. Hold it.
Durun, bakalım.
While it's true we might just be going off Luffy's gut feeling,
Luffy sadece hisleriyle hareket ediyor ama...
I believe he's right to think we don't need to be scared of him.
bence korkmamamız gerektiğinde haklı.
It's a stroke of luck that we met up with him...
Onunla tanışmamız şansımıza oldu.
because now we'll outsmart him.
Çünkü ondan daha akıllı davranacağız.
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei is...
Bay 2, Bon Clay-sama'nın...
Un, deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois!
What's "four" again?
''Dört'' ne demekti?
somehow in a very good mood.
nedense keyfi yerinde.
I made some new friends today!
Bugün yeni arkadaşlar edindim!
Sea Cat (Sea Monster) Territory: The Coast of Sandy Island
Deniz Kedisi (Deniz Canavarı) Bölge: Sandy Adası'nın Kıyısı
Something popped up!
Bir şey çıktı!
A sea cat!
Deniz kedisi!
It's a sea monster!
Deniz canavarı!
It's our first meal in four days!
Dört günün ardından ilk yemeğimiz!
It's food!
Yemek bu!
We're on the right track.
Doğru yolda ilerliyoruz.
I hope we get there soon.
Umarım yakın zamanda varırız.
Food!
Yemek!
Whoa! It's backing away!
Oha! Geri çekiliyor!
Go back! Full reverse!
Geriye! Full geri!
W-W-W-W-W-W-We can't!
Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Yapamayız!
Oh!
Oh!
Don't let it get away! We have to capture it!
Kaçmasına izin vermeyin! Onu yakalamalıyız!
Now, how would you like to be cooked, cat monster?!
Şimdi seni nasıl pişirelim, canavar kedi?!
You can't!
Yapamazsınız!
Vivi! You jerk! What are you doing?!
Vivi! Aptal! Ne yaptığını sanıyorsun?!
Wh... Why... Vivi?
N... Neden... Vivi-chan?
You can't eat it!
Yiyemezsiniz!
Sea cats are a sacred animal in Alabasta!
Deniz kedileri, Alabasta'da kutsal kabul edilir!
Tell us sooner!
Erken söylesene!
The sea's full of all kinds of creatures!
Denizde bir sürü yaratık var!
You've got a ways to go if you're scared of things like that.
Ondan korktuysanız daha çok yolunuz var.
Okay then!
Pekâlâ!
Here's a story all about how I bravely fought off sea kings in the Calm Belt.
Size Calm Belt'de deniz krallarıyla nasıl cesurca savaştığımı anlatayım.
Fought off sea kings?!
Deniz krallarıyla mı savaştın?!
Big ones! They were this big!
Çok büyüklerdi! Aha bu kadar!
O-Our food got away...
K-Kaçtı gitti, yemeğimiz...
It will all be okay! You'll soon have plenty to fill your belly!
Endişelenme! Yakında karnını doyuracak kadar yiyecek seni bekliyor!
Really?! What kind of cat will appear next time?!
Harbi mi?! Bu sefer nasıl bir kediyle karşılaşacağız?!
Vivi! The wind and weather seem to be stabilizing.
Vivi! Rüzgâr ve hava sakinleşiyor gibi gözüküyor.
Yes.
Evet.
We've entered Alabasta's climate area.
Alabasta'nın iklimine giriyoruz.
A sea cat appearing is a sure sign, too.
Deniz kedisiyle de karşılaşmamızdan belliydi.
And just look behind us.
Arkamızdaki manzara da muhtemelen...
More proof Alabasta's close by, right?
Alabasta'ya yaklaştığımızın kanıtı.
There are so many ships! When did that happen?!
Bir sürü gemi! Ne ara geldiler?!
Hey! They're all flying Baroque Works' colors!
Hepsinin de Baroque Works sembolleri var!
Its employees have started gathering.
Elemanları toplanmaya başladı.
They're most likely the billions, the officer agents' subordinates.
Büyük ihtimalle bunlar rütbeli ajanların astları, milyarlar.
Then there are at least 200 men out there.
O zaman en az 200 adam var orada.
In point of fact, they're the 200 elites of Baroque Works.
Daha doğrusu onlar, Baroque Works'ün 200 seçkini.
The bounty hunters at Whisky Peak don't even compare.
Whisky Peak'teki ödül avcıları bununla kıyaslanamaz bile.
Should we fire at them while we can?!
Fırsatımız varken ateş etsek mi?!
Let's get the drop on them!
Ateş edelim gitsin!
It's quicker if we go there and beat them up!
Yanlarına gidip de dövsek daha hızlı olur!
No, wait! We gotta eat first!
Durun! Önce karnımızı doyurmalıyız!
It'd be dumb to bother with those small-timers.
O küçük balıklarla uğraşmak aptalca olur.
He's right.
Haklı.
If we lose sight of our real target, we're done for.
Asıl amacımızı kaybedersek, vay halimize.
And there are only eight of us.
Hem zaten, sadece 8 kişiyiz.
Just... tie it tightly.
Her neyse, sıkıca bağlayın.
Our enemy this time is overly secretive.
Bu seferki rakibimiz oldukça ketum.
Perfect.
Anlıyorum.
These will help us tell who our real crewmates are.
Bunlar, birbirimizi ayırt etmemizi sağlayacak.
Does that Clone-Clone Fruit guy really
O Klon-Klon Meyvesi yiyen adam,
become so similar when he transforms?
dönüşünce çok mu benziyor cidden?
Seeing is believing! It's not just "similar,"
Görmen lazım! Benzemiyor ki...
it's identical!
aynısı!
It's too bad! You should've seen it. We even danced with him.
Yazık ki kaçırdın! Onunla dans ettiğimiz bile oldu.
Knowing someone like that is among our enemy,
Düşmanlarımız arasında böyleleri varken,
we can't carelessly act alone.
tek başımıza düşüncesizce hareket edemeyiz.
Hey, what should I do?
Hey, ben ne yapmalıyım?
Ahh... Do what you can do. You don't have to do anything more.
Ahh... Ne yapabilirsen... Fazlasına gerek yok.
It's okay to run away from an enemy you can't defeat!
Yenemediğin bir düşmandan kaçmak sorun değil!
Are you talking to him or yourself?
Bunu ona mı söylüyorsun, kendine mi?
What I can do, huh?
Ne yapabilirsem, ha?
Got it!
Anladım!
I can see the island now!
Ada göründü!
We'll visit Nanohana, that town ahead, but we need to hide the ship.
Nanohana'ya gideceğiz ama önce gemiyi saklamalıyız.
Alright! So, no matter what happens,
Tamamdır! Öyleyse ne olursa olsun,
our left arms prove that we're definitely crewmates!
bu kolumuzdaki şey, tayfadan olduğumuzun kanıtıdır.
Now, let's get ashore!
Şimdi, karaya çıkalım!
To a restaurant! Oh, and to Alabasta.
Önce restorana! Sonra Alabasta'ya.
– As a side note?
– Sonra mı?
Our enemy this time is a group of assassins, Luffy.
Bu seferki düşmanımız bir suikastçi grubu, Luffy.
Yeah. That's right.
Evet. Öyle.
Be careful about acting on instinct, okay?
İçgüdüyle hareket ederken tedbirli ol, tamam mı?
You're right. I got it. Yeah! That's right! Yeah! Got it!
Haklısın. Anladım. Evet! Doğru! Evet! Anladım!